Guide to the Edwin Warriner Papers and Photographs, 1790-1958 1977.255
Brooklyn Historical Society
- 2. Photographs and Other Images, circa 1850-circa 1890; 0.41 Linear Feet
  - Fletcher, Charles (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Fordham, Stephen (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 3)
  - Foss, C. D. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Foster (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Fox, H. J. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Francis, Abram S. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Frost, T. P. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Gillies, W. W. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 2)
  - Gibson, Thomas (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 4)
  - Gilbert, G. S. (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 5)
  - Gilbert, R. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Gilder, J. L. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Gilder, W. H. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Glover, C. E. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 2)
  - Glover, H. C. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Goodsell, G. H. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Green (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 5)
  - Grue (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 6)
  - Hadley (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 6)
  - Hammond, J. R. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 2)
  - Hammond, Samuel M. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Harper, Mrs. (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 7)
  - Hatfield, W. F. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Haynes, Emory J. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hill, F. C. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 2)
  - Hill, George (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hill, W. T. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hollis, George (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 2)
  - Holmes, David (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Horne, J. W. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Howe, J. M. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Howell, Daniel W. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hubbard, R. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hubbell, G. A. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hubbell, Nathan (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hunt, Jr., A. (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 8)
  - Husted, Harvey (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - James, E. L. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - James, John (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Jessop, Robert (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, S. F. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Jost, C (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Kellogg, N. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Kelly, William V. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Kelsey (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 7)
  - Kennaday, John (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 9)
  - King, S. W. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Krioteller (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Laine, G. N. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Landon, S. (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 10)
  - Lane, O. C. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Lattian, H. D. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Layton (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Leek, J. W. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Levings, N. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Livingston, Henry M. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Losee (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Luckey, Samuel (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Matthias, J. J. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - McAllister, W. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - McCain, Alexander (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 8)
  - McKillop (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Mead, Nathaniel (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 2)
  - Merwin, S. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Charles M. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 2)
  - Mitchell, J. S. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Nadal, B. H. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Nash, A. (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 11)
  - Nash, J. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Norris, W. H. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Oakley, P. C. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 3)
  - Olmstead, M. N. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Osborn, Elbert (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Osborn, T.G. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Osborn, Thomas G. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Pease, J. M. (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 9)
  - Pease, L. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Peck, George (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Peck, John L. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 3)
  - Pelton, C.F. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder -)
  - Perry, J. H. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Phoebus, William (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Pilsbury, B. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Platt, S. H. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Putney, R. S. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 3)
  - Redford, B. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Reeve, B. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Reeves (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Reid, J. M. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Remington, S. (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 12)
  - Rice, Phineas (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Richardson, M. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Robinson, W. S. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Ross, William (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Sandford, P. P. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Scudder, Moses L. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Sewall, T. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Shaffer, J. N. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Sillick, B. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Simmons (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Simonson, W. H. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Abrahams (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 10)
  - Smith, D. K. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Smith, J. G. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Staats, Henry T. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Stansbury, J. H. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Stearns (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Stevens, A. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Stevens, A. C. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Stillman, S. L. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Strong, S. S. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Tackaberry, J. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Taylor, G. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Thomas, J. C. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Thompson, John Ray (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 3)
  - Tibbals, Nathan (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 3)
  - Tower, F. P. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Traumer, J. M. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Twiddy, William (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Vail, John (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 13)
  - Wake, Jr., R. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Wake, William (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 14)
  - Warren (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Warriner, Edwin (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 15)
  - Warriner, Edwin (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Washburn, E (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Watkins, W. F. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Watson, Richard (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Webb, Thomas (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Weed, L. S. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Whedon, D. D. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Whedon, John S. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - White, N. (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 11)
  - Wild, J. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Willett, William Marinus (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Wing, C. S. (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 16)
  - Wood, J. W. B. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Woolsey, E. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified Ministers (4) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified Minister (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified Minister (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified ministers (2) (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 12)
  - Dix Hills (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - First Methodist Church (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 4)
  - Freeport (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Greenport (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Huntington (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Islip New M. E. Church (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Northport (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Pearsalls (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Port Jefferson (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Port Washington (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Riverhead (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Rockville Center (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Sag Harbor (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Sayville (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Second Methodist Church (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 4)
  - Southold (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Stone House (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Stony Brook (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Union Church (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 4)
- 3. Later Additions to the Collection, 1900-1958; 0.42 Linear Feet
  This series consists mostly of printed material from various Methodist churches on Long Island. The majority of these documents are special anniversary publications that include historical information about the church. Also in this series are a few manuscript writings, including poems, sermons, and biographical notes related to Methodist ministers.
  The series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Amityville: First Methodist Church, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Babylon Methodist Church, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Bayville Methodist Church, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn: Andrews Meth. Church, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn: Bay Ridge M. E. Church, circa 1930 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn: Bethelship Church, circa 1930 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn: Bushwick Ave Meth. Church, 1914, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn: Flatlands M. E. Church, 1901 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn: Fourth Ave Meth. Church, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn: Goodsell Memorial M. E. Church, 1913, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn: Immanuel Swedish Methodist Church, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Brooklyn: Janes M. E. Church, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn: New York Ave. M. E. Church, 1906 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn: Nostrand-DeKalb M. E. Church, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn: Prospect Ave. M. E. Church, 1911 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn: South Third St Methodist Church, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Brooklyn: St. Johns M. E. Church, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "Cape Farewell", 1927 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - "An Every Morning Prayer", 1927 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - "The Business of Making Friends", circa 1927 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Commack Methodist Church, 1949, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Corona: First M. E. Church, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - East Moriches Centennial Methodist Church, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Elmhurst: First Methodist Church, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Flushing: First Methodist Church, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Freeport M. E. Church, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Greenport: First M. E. Church, 1900, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Hauppauge M. E. Church, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Jamaica: First M. E. Church, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Kelly, William V. documents, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - "A Historical View of Methodism on Western Long Island", circa 1935 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Maspeth Methodist Church, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Middle Village (Newborn) M. E. Church, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Northport: St. Paul's M. E. Church, 1933, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Oyster Bay: St. Paul's Methodist Church, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Peck, George C., circa 1927 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Rockville Center: St. Mark's Methodist Church, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Searingtown M. E. Church, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Smithtown Branch and Smithtown Landing M. E. Churches, circa 1928 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Weed, Levi, circa 1952 (Box 15, Folder 33)